Library. University Librarian. Administrative files UARC.0377
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Collection Development 2.095, 1977-1984.; 891952; Includes Ad Hoc Committee correspondence 6.349 (Box 306, Folder 2-3)
- Collective Bargaining 2.098., 891950 (Box 306, Folder 4)
- College of Fine Arts., 1980-1988.; 891949 (Box 306, Folder 5)
- College Library 2.100., 1983-1984.; 891948 (Box 306, Folder 6-8)
- Audio Facility for the College Library. C.B. Hagen., 1966.; 891947 (Box 306, Folder 9)
- Committee for Library of the Future., 1984-1986; 891946 (Box 306, Folder 10-12)
- Will Connell Collection., 1982-1987; 891944; Correspondence covering attempts by Will Connell, Jr. to recover the collection. (Box 306, Folder 12)
- Communications Studies archives., 1987.; 891942 (Box 306, Folder 13)
- Computerized Information Services Unit., 1987; 891941 (Box 306, Folder 14)
- Computer Reference Services Operation Group 2.112., 1975-1978; 1987-1991; 891940; Includes Statistics Procedures and Reports (Box 306, Folder 15-17)
- Conflict of Interest code., 1986.; 891937 (Box 306, Folder 17-18)
- Contract and Grant, Office of (correspondence)., 1980-1983.; 891934 (Box 306, Folder 20-21)
- Copyright., 1967-1986.; 891932 (Box 306, Folder 22-26)
- Cornell University 5.145. Collection Development and Management Project, 1977-1981.; 891929 (Box 306, Folder 27)
- Council on Library Resources., 1977-1987.; 891928; Includes Management Interim Program and Wye Plantation Forum II [preservation] (Box 306, Folder 28-30)
- Council on International and Comparative Studies 7.175., 1981.; 891924 (Box 306, Folder 31)
- Committee on Undergrad Curriculum (CUCC), 1986-1987.; 891923 (Box 306, Folder 32)
- Ted Cummings Memorial Proposal., 1983.; 891922 (Box 306, Folder 33)
- C - miscellaneous 5.055., 891921 (Box 306, Folder 34)
- Louise M. Darling correspondence., 1986-1987.; 891920 (Box 307, Folder 1)
- Data Archives Committee., 1963-1979.; 891919 (Box 307, Folder 2)
- Chronological files., 1950-1965; n.d.; 891918 (Box 307, Folder 3-9)
- Library Staff Association., 891917 (Box 307, Folder 10)
- Campbell Book Collection Contest - Saul Cohen lecture., 1965 Feb 17.; 891916 (Box 307, Folder 11)
- Clark Library miscellaneous., 1940's-1960's.; 891915 (Box 307, Folder 12)
- Librarians Association., 891914 (Box 307, Folder 13)
- Acquisitions Department annual report., 1964/1965.; 891913 (Box 307, Folder 14)
- Richard Abel Physical Sciences blanket purchase order., 891912 (Box 307, Folder 15)
- Stechert-Hafner Latin-American blanket purchase order., 1965/1966.; 891911 (Box 307, Folder 16)
- Richard Abel correspondence and U.S.S.R. blanket purchase order., 1969-1973.; 891910 (Box 307, Folder 17)
- Advocate books (Philippines) blanket purchase order and correspondence., 1964-1967.; 891909 (Box 307, Folder 18)
- Artia (Czechoslovakia) blanket purchase order correspondence., 1964-1965.; 891908 (Box 307, Folder 19)
- Cartimex (Rumania) blanket purchase order correspondence., 1964-1965.; 891907 (Box 307, Folder 20)
- Draugas (Lithuanian) blanket purchase order correspondence., 1964-1965.; 891906 (Box 307, Folder 21)
- Eleftheroudakis (Greece) blanket purchase order correspondence., 1966.; 891905 (Box 307, Folder 22)
- Far Eastern (Japan) blanket purchase order correspondence., 1963-1965.; 891904 (Box 307, Folder 23)
- Harrassowitz engineering and mathematical science blanket purchase order correspondence., 1965-1966.; 891903 (Box 307, Folder 24)
- Mladost (Yugoslavia) blanket purchase order correspondence., 1964-1965.; 891902 (Box 307, Folder 25)
- Nijhoff (Netherlands) engineering and mathematical science blanket purchase order correspondence., 1965.; 891901 (Box 307, Folder 26)
- Soo Do (Korea) blanket purchase order correspondence., 1964-1967.; 891900 (Box 307, Folder 27)
- Stevens & Brown (England) blanket purchase order correspondence., 1965.; 891899 (Box 307, Folder 28)
- United Publishing Center (Taiwan) blanket purchase order correspondence., 1963-1965.; 891898 (Box 307, Folder 29)
- Whitcomb & Tombs (New Zealand) blanket purchase order correspondence., 1963-1964.; 891897 (Box 307, Folder 30)
- Richard Abel Education and Psychology blanket purchase order correspondence., 1970-1974.; 891895 (Box 307, Folder 32)
- Richard Abel blanket purchase order correspondence., 1964-1975.; 891894 (Box 307, Folder 33)
- Angus and Robertson (Australia) blanket purchase order correspondence., 1964-1970.; 891893 (Box 307, Folder 34)
- A/S Bokjhoernet (Norway) blanket purchase order correspondence., 1964-1970.; 891892 (Box 307, Folder 35)
- Alexander Broude music blanket purchase order correspondence., 1965-1970.; 891891 (Box 307, Folder 36)
- California Music Company Ethnomusicology blanket purchase order correspondence., 1965.; 891890 (Box 307, Folder 37)
- Co-operative Book Centre of Canada blanket purchase order correspondence., 1964-1970.; 891889 (Box 307, Folder 38)
- Discount Records Sound Recordings blanket purchase order correspondence., 1969-1970.; 891888 (Box 307, Folder 39)
- Dong Nam (Korea) blanket purchase order correspondence., 1967-1969.; 891887 (Box 307, Folder 40)
- Snaebjoern Jonsson or Snaebjarnar Jonssonar (Iceland) blanket purchase order correspondence., 1967-1970.; 891886 (Box 307, Folder 41)
- Maruzen (Japan) blanket purchase order correspondence., 1965-1969.; 891885 (Box 307, Folder 42)
- Oriental Book Co. (Hong Kong) blanket purchase order correspondence., 1963-1970.; 891884 (Box 307, Folder 43)
- Paul's Book Arcade (New Zealand) blanket purchase order correspondence., 1965-1972.; 891883 (Box 307, Folder 44)
- Philippine Education Co. blanket purchase order correspondence., 1966-1972.; 891882 (Box 307, Folder 45)
- AB Sandbergs Bokhandel (Sweden) blanket purchase order correspondence., 1964-1972.; 891881 (Box 307, Folder 46)
- IAC Joint SubCommittee of the Reference Services and Database Access Forums., 1991-1993.; 891880 (Box 307, Folder 47)
- Water Resources Archive., 1990-1991.; 891879 (Box 307, Folder 48)
- AB Nordiska Bokhandeln (Sweden) blanket purchase order correspondence., 1972-1974.; 891878 (Box 307, Folder 49)
- Deans luncheons., 1980-1981.; 891877 (Box 308, Folder 1)
- Deferred maintenance file., 1982-1983.; 891876 (Box 308, Folder 2)
- Departmental (non-affiliated) libraries census and survey., 1975-1981.; 891875 (Box 308, Folder 3)
- Development (UCLA Library)., 1986-1987.; 891874 (Box 308, Folder 4)
- Director of development search (UCLA Library)., 1986.; 891873 (Box 308, Folder 5)
- Disaster preparedness., 891872 (Box 308, Folder 6)
- Division of Library automation WYLBUR users., 1985.; 891871 (Box 308, Folder 7)
- Division of Library automation investigation., 1985.; 891870 (Box 308, Folder 8)
- Gilmore S. Wheeler. "An approach to short and long range planning for the Division of Library automation.", 1985.; 891869 (Box 308, Folder 9)
- Division of Library automation correspondence., 1976-1986.; 891868 (Box 308, Folder 10)
- Doctorate program assessment., 1983.; 891867 (Box 308, Folder 11)
- Richard Dougherty correspondence., 891866 (Box 308, Folder 12)
- Norman Dudley's retirement party., 1982 Oct 22.; 891865 (Box 308, Folder 13)
- DuBois papers., 1980.; 891864 (Box 308, Folder 14)
- D - miscellaneous 5.160., 891863 (Box 308, Folder 15)
- Education Psychology Library 2.140., 1976-1984.; 891862 (Box 308, Folder 16)
- Employee injuries "new file.", 891861 (Box 308, Folder 17)
- English Department., 891860 (Box 308, Folder 18)
- English Reading Room 2.155., 1977-1980.; 891859 (Box 308, Folder 19)
- English Reading Room - correspondence re: funding for 2.155., 1982.; 891858 (Box 308, Folder 20)
  Includes Chaucer portrait.
- English Reading Room - memos to R. Gibbs re: proposed withdrawal of funds., 1982.; 891857 (Box 308, Folder 21)
- Engineering/Math Sciences Library., 1977-1983.; 891856 (Box 308, Folder 22)
- Vice-Chancellor George Enoch., 1985-1986.; 891855 (Box 308, Folder 23)
- ERIC Clearinghouse 2.141., 891854 (Box 308, Folder 24)
- Equipment and furniture 2.163., 1977-1980.; 891853 (Box 308, Folder 25)
- Chicano Library resources at UCLA; compiled by R. Chabran, F. Garcia, with R. Rodriguez. Inst. of American Cultures., 1980.; 891852 (Box 308, Folder 26)
- Asian-American study center., 1977-1978.; 891851 (Box 308, Folder 27)
  Includes material relating to the Oriental (East Asian) Library.
- Afro-American Library resources at UCLA; compiled by N. Davis with L. Gutierrez, J. Leonard, M. Osborne. Inst. of American Cultures., 891850 (Box 308, Folder 28)
- American Indian Library resources at UCLA; compiled by V. Salabiye with M. Fraga, R. Jopling, H. Upton, L. Vaughn. Inst. of American Cultures., 1980.; 891849 (Box 308, Folder 29)
- Asian American Library resources at UCLA; compiled by J. Chomori with K. Kanatani. Inst. of American Cultures., 1980.; 891848 (Box 308, Folder 30)
- Ethnomusicology Archives 2.336., 1971-1982.; 891847 (Box 308, Folder 31)
- Exchange section 2.422., 1979.; 891846 (Box 308, Folder 32)
- Executive review (Library)., 1985.; 891845 (Box 308, Folder 33-34)
- Executive Vice Chancellor William Schaefer correspondence., 1984-1987.; 891844 (Box 308, Folder 35)
- Exhibits (Library)., 1977-1981.; 891843 (Box 308, Folder 36)
- Extended service hours., 1978-1979.; 891842 (Box 308, Folder 37)
- Extension (University Extension division) 7.268., 1980-1982.; 891841 (Box 308, Folder 38)
- E. miscellaneous., 891840 (Box 308, Folder 39)
- Facilities., 1980-1984.; 891839 (Box 308, Folder 40)
- Facilities request 2.168., 1983.; 891838 (Box 308, Folder 41)
- Faculty Center 7.305., 891837 (Box 308, Folder 42)
- Faculty newsletter., 1985-1986.; 891836 (Box 308, Folder 43)
- Faculty research lecture., 1984.; 891835 (Box 308, Folder 44)
- Financial status report, through April 1983., 891834 (Box 308, Folder 45)
- Fine arts libraries., 1984-1986.; 891833 (Box 308, Folder 46)
- Folklore Department., 1976-1977.; 891832 (Box 308, Folder 47)
- Foundation collection 2.396., 891831 (Box 308, Folder 48)
- Friends by-law., 1961.; 891830 (Box 308, Folder 49)
  Adopted 1961 Jan 23.
- Friends Council members., 1978; 1980; 1981.; 891829 (Box 308, Folder 50)
- MRLC facsimile numbers (alternate patron #)., 1978-1984.; 891828 (Box 308, Folder 51)
- Courtesy parking., 1976; 1982; 1983.; 891827 (Box 309, Folder 1)
- Friends of the UCLA Library, 1977-1989; 891826 (Box 309, Folder 2-309)
- Fuji UCLA project., 1982.; 891817 (Box 309, Folder 14)
- F - miscellaneous., 891816 (Box 309, Folder 15)
- David Gardner, President, University of California., 1984-1986.; 891815 (Box 309, Folder 16)
- Geology Library., 1978-1982.; 891814 (Box 309, Folder 17)
- Getty Foundation., 891813 (Box 309, Folder 18)
- Getty Trust., 1983-1987.; 891812 (Box 309, Folder 19)
- Getty Center for the History of Art and the Humanities., 1986.; 891811 (Box 309, Folder 20)
- Getty Retrospective Conversion Project funding., 1985.; 891810 (Box 309, Folder 21)
- Getty Museum publicity., 1985.; 891809 (Box 309, Folder 22)
- Gifts (Library Gifts section; RKO Archives)., 1982-1984.; 891808 (Box 309, Folder 23)
- Gift correspondence, 891807; Includes A-W correspondence and John Vincent (Box 309, Folder 24-36)
- Gifts and exchange., 1975-1982.; 891794 (Box 309, Folder 37)
- Donors to the Library., 1981.; 891793 (Box 309, Folder 38)
- Gordon and Breach., 891792 (Box 309, Folder 39)
- Graduate Division., 1978-1979.; 891791 (Box 309, Folder 40)
- Graduate School of Education Doctoral Alumni Association 1983 meeting., 1982-1983.; 891790 (Box 309, Folder 41)
- Graduate School of Library and Information Science "Predictors of student performance with emphasis on gender and ethnic determinants.", c. 1987.; 891789 (Box 309, Folder 42)
- Grants NEH L.A. daily news morgue photographic negatives; application form., 1984; n.d.; 891788 (Box 309, Folder 43)
- Department of Education grant (Wittenborg and Cheng)., 1986-1987.; 891787 (Box 309, Folder 44)
- Grunwald Center for the Graphic Arts., 891786 (Box 309, Folder 45)
- Guest list for Professor Bruman's reception February 11., 891785 (Box 309, Folder 46)
- G - miscellaneous correspondence., 1979-1981.; 891784 (Box 309, Folder 47)
- Handicapped access., 891783 (Box 309, Folder 48)
- Vice Chancellor Adrian Harris., 1985-1987.; 891782 (Box 309, Folder 49)
- Harvard University., 1977.; 891781 (Box 309, Folder 50)
- Hayes/Council on Library Resources/UCLA Conference on Strategic Planning for Information Resources in the Research University, Malibu., 891780 (Box 309, Folder 51)
- Help meetings [ORION help display request form]., c. 198_.; 891779 (Box 309, Folder 52)
- Higher Education and National Affairs (American Council on Education vol. 33 no. 7 4/23/84)., 1984.; 891778 (Box 309, Folder 53)
- Hollywood Museum., 1982-1990.; 891777 (Box 309, Folder 54)
- Homosexuality - where to find information on in the Library., 1983.; 891776 (Box 309, Folder 55)
- Vice Chancellor Harold Horowitz correspondence., 1984-1987.; 891775 (Box 309, Folder 56)
- Humanities computing., 891774 (Box 309, Folder 57)
- Huntington Library., 1979; 1989.; 891773 (Box 309, Folder 58)
- H - miscellaneous (includes University of Houston)., 1977-1982.; 891772 (Box 309, Folder 59)
- IBM proposal for the campus library copying system., 891771 (Box 309, Folder 60)
- ID card (student)., 1976-1981.; 891770 (Box 309, Folder 61)
- IFLA (International Federation of Library Associations)., 1985-1987.; 891769 (Box 310, Folder 1)
- Institute of American Cultures 7.380., 1977-1980.; 891768 (Box 310, Folder 2)
  Includes 1977 Report of the Ad hoc Committee To Review the Ethnic Studies Centers Libraries in Campbell Hall.
- Institute of Industrial Relations., 1986.; 891767 (Box 310, Folder 3)
- Institute for Social Science Research 7.381., 1979-1981.; 891766 (Box 310, Folder 4)
- International and Comparative Studies, Institute of, 7.385., 1978.; 891765 (Box 310, Folder 5)
- International Studies and Overseas Program., 1987.; 891764 (Box 310, Folder 6)
  Includes announcement of Japan Research and Exchange Program.
- International and Comparative Studies, Institute of 7.385., 1977-1981.; 891763 (Box 310, Folder 7-9)
- International Association of Bibliophiles., 1985.; 891762 (Box 310, Folder 10)
- Inglewood Stack Annex 2.200., 891761 (Box 310, Folder 11)
- Intercampus activities fund props., 1979-1980.; 891760 (Box 310, Folder 12)
- Intercampus Transportation, Task Force on., 1981-1984.; 891759 (Box 310, Folder 13)
- Intercampus vehicle 2.206., 891758 (Box 310, Folder 14)
- Inter-library loan (ILL) 2.210., 1977-1984.; 891757 (Box 310, Folder 15)
- I -miscellaneous 5.255., 891756 (Box 310, Folder 16)
- Japan Exchange Program., 891755 (Box 310, Folder 17)
- Norah Jones., 1958-1986.; 891754 (Box 310, Folder 18)
- J -miscellaneous., 1977-1982.; 891753 (Box 310, Folder 19)
- K - miscellaneous 5.285., 1977-1982.; 891752 (Box 310, Folder 20)
  Includes correspondence about photos of Kindersley's Powell plaque.
- Henstell and Stein meeting, November 14, 1986 [L.A. Disc Voyager Press proposed project]., 891751 (Box 310, Folder 21)
- L.A. Disc/Voyager Press agreement., 1986.; 891750 (Box 310, Folder 22)
- Laboratory of Biomedical and Environmental Science 2.235., 1981-1982.; 891749 (Box 310, Folder 23)
- Lake Arrowhead Conference Center., 1984.; 891748 (Box 310, Folder 24)
- Latin American Center., 1976-1985.; 891747 (Box 310, Folder 25)
- LAUC Faculty Development Fund., 891746 (Box 310, Folder 26)
- LAUC general correspondence., 1985-1986.; 891745 (Box 310, Folder 27)
- LAUC research proposals., 1985.; 891744 (Box 310, Folder 28)
- Law Library 2.240., 1981-1987.; 891743 (Box 310, Folder 29-32)
- Law Library access., 1976-1984.; 891742 (Box 310, Folder 33)
- Law, School of., 1978-1980.; 891741 (Box 310, Folder 34)
- Legal documents 2.243., 891740 (Box 310, Folder 35)
- Lending code 2.245., 1977-1981.; 891739 (Box 310, Folder 36)
- Final report of lending code Committee; Senate Library Committee recommendations; summary of recommendations., 1977.; 891738 (Box 310, Folder 37)
- LARC Report (Lib Automation Review Committee)., 891737 (Box 311, Folder 1)
- Library Automatic Review Committee., 1987.; 891736 (Box 311, Folder 2)
- Leonardo Studies Center (Armand Hammer Center at UCLA)., 891735 (Box 311, Folder 3)
- Letter and Science, College., 891734 (Box 311, Folder 4)
- Library Accounting., 891733 (Box 311, Folder 5)
- Library administrative calendar 2.271., 891732 (Box 311, Folder 6)
- Library Assistant Series., 1983-; 891731 (Box 311, Folder 7)
- Library Administrative Network 2.255., 891730 (Box 311, Folder 8)
- Library Administrative Network Evaluation 2.255 EVAL., 891729 (Box 311, Folder 9)
- Statewide - Special Task Group on Restructuring Library Assistant Series., 1981-1982.; 891728 (Box 311, Folder 10)
- Library Card and Service Information., 891727 (Box 311, Folder 11)
- Library privileges 2.285., 891726 (Box 311, Folder 12)
- Library cards - special agreements - CSUC., 891725 (Box 311, Folder 13)
- Library Committees, Census of 2.260., 891724 (Box 311, Folder 14)
- Library of Congress., 891723 (Box 311, Folder 15)
- Library goals 2.283., 891722 (Box 311, Folder 16)
- Library privileges., 891721 (Box 311, Folder 17)
- Library Instruction Task Group #2 (Includes Report) 2.284., 891720 (Box 311, Folder 18)
- Library Orientation Program., 891719 (Box 311, Folder 19)
- Library Orientation tours., 891718 (Box 311, Folder 20)
- Library regulations 2.293., 891717 (Box 311, Folder 21)
- UCLA Library - Human Subject Protection Statement of Exemption 2.283a., 891716 (Box 311, Folder 22)
- Library Science Task Force Item #1, 2., 891715 (Box 311, Folder 23)
- Library Service to Undergraduates, Task Force On., 1979.; 891714 (Box 311, Folder 24-27)
- Local automation UC Libraries., 891713 (Box 311, Folder 28)
- LA County Public Library., 891712 (Box 311, Folder 29)
- LA Public Library 5.320., 891711 (Box 311, Folder 30)
- Los Angeles Public Library (LAPL)., 891710 (Box 311, Folder 31)
- L - miscellaneous 5.300., 891709 (Box 311, Folder 32)
- MacIntyre Portrait., 891708 (Box 311, Folder 33)
- Mail room 7.445., 891707 (Box 311, Folder 34)
- Mailgrams (Western Union)., 891706 (Box 311, Folder 35)
- Management, Graduate School of., 891705 (Box 311, Folder 36)
- Graduate Mathematics Reading Room 7.461., 891704 (Box 311, Folder 37)
- Maintenance, Libraries 2.310., 891703 (Box 311, Folder 38)
- Management Library 2.315., 891702 (Box 311, Folder 39)
- Management Review Analysis Program (MRAP) 2.317., 891701 (Box 311, Folder 40)
- Management Services Officer Series., 1983-; 891700 (Box 311, Folder 41)
- Management and Professional Program (MAP)., 891699 (Box 311, Folder 42)
- Map Library 2.320., 1959-1985.; 891698 (Box 312, Folder 1)
- Mayor's Advisory Committee Regarding the Robert F. Kennedy Assassination Investigation Materials., 1986.; 891697 (Box 312, Folder 2-4)
- Metropolitan Cooperative Library System (MCLS)., 1986-1987.; 891696 (Box 312, Folder 5)
- Joint Senate - Administrative Committee on Media Materials., 1984.; 891695 (Box 312, Folder 6)
- Media Center., 1977.; 891694 (Box 312, Folder 7)
- Media Archives Committee., 891693 (Box 312, Folder 8)
- Medicine, School of., 1985.; 891692 (Box 312, Folder 9)
- MELVYL-MEDLINE Project., 1984-1985.; 891691 (Box 312, Folder 10)
- Medieval and Renaissance Studies Center., 891690 (Box 312, Folder 11)
- Mental Retardation Research Center., 1983.; 891689 (Box 312, Folder 12)
- Merit and Promotion Recommendations, Library., 1984.; 891688 (Box 312, Folder 13)
- Microform Holdings, Union List of., 891687 (Box 312, Folder 14)
- Microforms 2.330., 1977-1980.; 891686 (Box 312, Folder 15)
- Mid-Management Task Group., 891685 (Box 312, Folder 16)
- Henry Miller materials., 891684 (Box 312, Folder 17)
- MUGGERS [microcomputer support group]., 1985.; 891683 (Box 312, Folder 18)
- Mitchell Fund (Music) #940170 includes 1975-1976 Project Planning Guide for Schoenberg Hall Addition., 1975-1984.; 891682 (Box 312, Folder 19)
- Music Library 2.335., 1977-1989.; 891681 (Box 312, Folder 20)
- M - miscellaneous., 1979-1982.; 891680 (Box 312, Folder 21)
- NACO costs meeting., 1984 Apr 30.; 891679 (Box 312, Folder 22)
- NCLIS [National Commission on Libraries and Information Science] Fed. Support of Lib. & Info Services., 1978 Sep 14.; 891678 (Box 312, Folder 23)
- National Endowment for the Arts Grant #A 40-20-223B 7.500., 1977-1981.; 891677 (Box 312, Folder 24)
- National Endowment for the Humanities, 1976-1985.; 891676; Includes Challenge Grant, Bibliographic control of Belt Library, LA Daily News conservation, Neat East photographs, and Luciano Berio bibliography (Box 312, Folder 25-31)
- National Library of Medicine., 891670 (Box 312, Folder 32)
- Building Committee 7.500 Motion Picture/Television Archive Facility., 1973-1977.; 891669 (Box 312, Folder 33)
- Near Eastern Center 7.505., 1977-1980.; 891668 (Box 312, Folder 34)
- National Endowment for the Humanities - College Library Program., 1978.; 891667 (Box 312, Folder 35)
- National Endowment for the Humanities - Challenge Grant., 1978-1982.; 891666 (Box 312, Folder 36-37)
- Oral History [UCLA Monthly]., 1986 Jan-Feb.; 891665 (Box 312, Folder 38)
- Los Angeles Art CommUnity: Group Portrait Project., 1978.; 891664 (Box 312, Folder 39)
- Provost Ray Orbach., 1984.; 891663 (Box 312, Folder 40)
- Massachusetts Institute of Technology Report. Director of Libraries., 1983-1984.; 891662 (Box 312, Folder 41)
- Richard Rudolph Dedication (Oriental Library)., 1981 Apr 10.; 891661 (Box 313, Folder 1)
- Oriental (East Asian) Library 2.350., 1977-1982.; 891660 (Box 313, Folder 2)
- Oriental (East Asian) Library., 891659 (Box 313, Folder 3)
- ORION software., 1980-1986.; 891658 (Box 313, Folder 4)
- ORION User Services., 1984.; 891657 (Box 313, Folder 5)
- O - miscellaneous., 891656 (Box 313, Folder 6)
- Pacific Rim Libraries 5.447., 1983-1984.; 891655 (Box 313, Folder 7)
- Parking Service., 1977-1980.; 891654 (Box 313, Folder 8)
- Party Invitations, Library., c. 1980-1983.; 891653 (Box 313, Folder 9)
- Retirement party for Jim Mink and Brooke Whiting., 1983 Jun 17.; 891652 (Box 313, Folder 10)
- Patron complaints., 1979-1982.; 891651 (Box 313, Folder 11-13)
- Pearl, Judea., 1984-1985.; 891650 (Box 313, Folder 14)
- Lawrence Clark Powell's 75th Anniversary Celebration., 1981 Sep 13.; 891649 (Box 313, Folder 15)
- Performing Arts Library Planning Grant (Library Services and Construction Act)., 1984-1985.; 891648 (Box 313, Folder 16)
- Photographic Services., 1983-1984.; 891647 (Box 313, Folder 17)
- Photographic Services., 891646 (Box 313, Folder 18)
- Physical plant 7.558., 1979-1980.; 891645 (Box 313, Folder 19-20)
- Physics Library 2.360., 891644 (Box 313, Folder 21)
- Physical Sciences Library 2.358., 1977-1984.; 891643 (Box 313, Folder 22)
- University of California Assistant Vice-President for Library Plans and Policies., 1984.; 891642 (Box 313, Folder 23)
- Plan, The (University of California: Plan for Development)., 1977-1984.; 891641 (Box 313, Folder 24)
- UCLA Library in the 1980's., 891640 (Box 313, Folder 25)
- Draft of the University of California Academic Plan., 1980.; 891639 (Box 313, Folder 26)
- Plan, Library., 891638 (Box 313, Folder 27)
- First draft of revision of Plan for Development May 20, 1987., 891637 (Box 313, Folder 28)
- Plan, The (University of California Libraries: A Plan for Development 1978-1988) "Salmon Plan.", 1977.; 891636 (Box 313, Folder 29)
- Planning Office meeting., 1982.; 891635 (Box 313, Folder 30)
- Police Department., 1980.; 891634 (Box 313, Folder 31)
- Political Science Department., 1977-1981.; 891633 (Box 313, Folder 32)
- Powell Library Planning Committee 7.572., 1979-1981.; 891632 (Box 313, Folder 33-34)
- Lawrence Clark Powell., 1980-1987.; 891631 (Box 313, Folder 35)
- Southern Regional Compact Shelving Facility G.271 1978., 891630 (Box 313, Folder 36)
- Powell Library, 1978-1986; 891629; Includes Language Learning Labs and Planning committee (Box 313, Folder 37-39)